Guide to the Office of the Dean, Washington Square College and Washington Square and University College of Arts and Science 1929-1984 (Bulk 1951-1980) RG.19
New York University Archives
- Series II: Additional Dean's Files, 167548
  - University Without Walls, 1969-1971; 167949 (Box 45, Folder 36)
  - University Without Walls - London, 1971-1974; 167948 (Box 45, Folder 37)
  - University Without Walls, 1972-1974; 167947 (Box 45, Folder 38)
  - University Without Walls, 1974; 167946 (Box 45, Folder 39)
  - University Without Walls (Antioch), 1970-1971; 167945 (Box 45, Folder 40)
  - Urban Health Affairs, 1968-1971; 167944 (Box 45, Folder 41)
  - Urban Studies (Landmarks Scholars Program - Fine Arts), 1974; 167943 (Box 45, Folder 42)
  - Urban Studies, 1965-1970; 167942 (Box 45, Folder 43)
  - Center for Urban Studies, 1970; 167941 (Box 45, Folder 44)
  - Urban University, 1970; 167940 (Box 45, Folder 45)
  - Immanuel Velikovsky, 1967-1968; 167939 (Box 45, Folder 46)
  - The American Institute for Verdi Studies Newsletter, 1976; 167938 (Box 45, Folder 47)
  - Veterans Recruitment, 1972-1973; 167937 (Box 45, Folder 48)
  - Vice President Armstrong, 1955-1958; 167936 (Box 45, Folder 49)
  - Vice President Berezin, 1968; 167935 (Box 45, Folder 50)
  - Vice President Campbell, 1976; 167934 (Box 45, Folder 51)
  - Vice President De Capriles, 1968-1974; 167933 (Box 45, Folder 52)
  - Vice President David Robinson, 1967-1975; 167932 (Box 45, Folder 53)
  - Vice President Williams, 1962-1967; 167931 (Box 45, Folder 54)
  - "The Villager", 1974; 167930 (Box 45, Folder 55)
  - Violet Fraternity Council, 1963-1967; 167929 (Box 45, Folder 56)
  - Virginia State College at Norfolk, 1967-1968; 167928 (Box 45, Folder 57)
  - Visiting Scholars, 1964-1973; 167927 (Box 45, Folder 58)
  - Visiting Students Program, 1973-1974; 167926 (Box 46, Folder 1)
    bar code #: 3 1142 04227105 9
  - Visitors Program State Dept Bureau of Education and Cultural Affairs, 1969; 167925 (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Voice Party, 1967; 167924 (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Professor Von Guerard, 1963-1972; 167923 (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Voting Lists, 1972-1973; 167922 (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - Wagreich, 1963-1964; 167921 (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - Ingo Walter, GBA, 1969; 167920 (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - Reports from Washington, 1970; 167919 (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - Washington Square Committee, 1970; 167918 (Box 46, Folder 9)
  - Washington Square Review, 1965-1972; 167917 (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - Washington Square Village, 1963-1976; 167916 (Box 46, Folder 11)
  - Watt Lecture, 1968; 167915 (Box 46, Folder 12)
  - A Way with Words Conference, 1968; 167914 (Box 46, Folder 13)
  - Curriculum for Weekend College, 1972-1973; 167913 (Box 46, Folder 14)
  - Rene Wellek, 1964-1965; 167912 (Box 46, Folder 15)
  - Dr. Whiteman, 1967-1971; 167911 (Box 46, Folder 16)
  - Who's Who Recommendations and Info, 1973; 167910 (Box 46, Folder 17)
  - Wide World Lecture Bureau, 1965; 167909 (Box 46, Folder 18)
  - Wilderness Workshop, 1977; 167908 (Box 46, Folder 19)
  - Mabel Williamson, 1968-1973; 167907 (Box 46, Folder 20)
  - RBW Chairman Minutes, 1974-1975; 167906 (Box 46, Folder 21)
  - Dean Winder, 1969-1976; 167905 (Box 46, Folder 22)
  - Wisconsin Universities UN Seminar, 1966; 167904 (Box 46, Folder 23)
  - Withdrawals, 1966; 167903 (Box 46, Folder 24)
  - Women, 1970-1973; 167902 (Box 46, Folder 25)
  - Work-Study Program, 1969-1971; 167901 (Box 46, Folder 26)
  - Association of Women Students, 1964-1966; 167900 (Box 46, Folder 27)
  - Woodrow Wilson National Fellowship, 1968-1971; 167899 (Box 46, Folder 28)
  - World Microfilms Publications, 1975-1976; 167898 (Box 46, Folder 29)
  - Writing Center, 1964-1969; 167897 (Box 46, Folder 30)
  - Xerox, 1973-1974; 167896 (Box 46, Folder 31)
  - Xerox College Publishing, 1971-1974; 167895 (Box 46, Folder 32)
  - Yearbook, 1974; 167894 (Box 46, Folder 33)
  - Thomas Brophy - Sunrise Semester, 1979; 167893 (Box 47, Folder 1)
    bar code #: 3 1142 04227106 7
  - Sunrise Semester, 1983-1984; 167892 (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Sunrise Semester Contract, 1963-1978; 167891 (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - Sunrise Semester Course Distribution, 1966; 167890 (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - Sunrise Semester Course in Islam, 1980; 167889 (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - Sunrise Semester Funding, 1972-1980; 167888 (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - Sunrise Semester Fundraising, 1971-1972; 167887 (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - Sunrise Semester Grant Proposals, 1980-1981; 167886 (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - Sunrise Semester History, 1980-1981; 167885 (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - Sunrise Semester in Other Colleges, 1967-1979; 167884 (Box 47, Folder 10)
  - Sunrise Semester Job Descriptions, 1980; 167883 (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - Sunrise Semester Misc., 1971-1978; 167882 (Box 47, Folder 12)
  - Sunrise Semester Past Courses, undated; 167881 (Box 47, Folder 13)
  - Sunrise Semester Publicity, 1978-1981; 167880 (Box 47, Folder 14)
  - Sunrise Semester Sawhill Course, 1978-1981; 167879 (Box 47, Folder 15)
  - Sunrise Semester, 1980; 167878 (Box 47, Folder 16)
  - Sunrise Semester New Courses, 1979-1980; 167877 (Box 47, Folder 17)
  - Sunrise Semester New Funding Ideas, 1980; 167876 (Box 47, Folder 18)
  - Sunrise Semester News Articles, 1971-1980; 167875 (Box 47, Folder 19)
  - Sunrise Semester, 1981; 167874 (Box 47, Folder 20)
  - Sunrise Semester Amy Ostrawer Research Consultant, 1980-1981; 167873 (Box 47, Folder 21)
  - Sunrise Semester Ideas for Courses, 1980-1981; 167872 (Box 47, Folder 22)
  - Sunrise Semester Funding, 1980-1981; 167871 (Box 47, Folder 23)
  - Sunrise Semester CBS Contracts and Agreements, 1980-1981; 167870 (Box 47, Folder 24)
  - Sunrise Semester Courses, 1980-1981; 167869 (Box 47, Folder 25)
  - Sunrise Semester Operating Budget, 1980-1981; 167868 (Box 47, Folder 26)
  - Sunrise Semster Womenand Men in Changing Society, 1980-1981; 167867 (Box 47, Folder 27)
  - Sunrise Semster Bills, 1980; 167866 (Box 47, Folder 28)
  - Sunrise Semester, 1978-1979; 167865 (Box 47, Folder 29)
  - Sunrise Semester Budget, 1979-1980; 167864 (Box 47, Folder 30)
  - Sunrise Semester Curriculum Committee, 1980; 167863 (Box 47, Folder 31)
  - Sunrise Semester ECRs, 1978-1979; 167862 (Box 47, Folder 32)
  - Sunrise Semester, 1979; 167861 (Box 47, Folder 33)
  - Sunrise Semester Ancient Egyptian Art, 1979; 167860 (Box 47, Folder 34)
  - FAS Meeting Minutes, 1980-1981; 167859 (Box 47, Folder 35)
  - FAS Budget Proposal, 1979-1980; 167858 (Box 47, Folder 36)
  - FAS Meeting Minutes, 1979-1980; 167857 (Box 47, Folder 37)
  - FAS Meeting Minutes, 1978-1979; 167856 (Box 47, Folder 38)
  - FAS Meeting Minutes, 1977-1978; 167855 (Box 47, Folder 39)
  - FAS Meeting Minutes, 1977-1978; 167854 (Box 47, Folder 40)
  - Security Committee, Information about Members, 1980; 167853 (Box 47, Folder 41)
  - Secutiry Committee: Minutes and Agendas, 1980; 167852 (Box 47, Folder 42)
  - Security Committee, 1980; 167851 (Box 47, Folder 43)
  - Security Input Firm Faculty, 1980; 167850 (Box 47, Folder 44)
  - Security Protection Services: Reports to Edward Schnell and Staff Reports, 1979-1980; 167849 (Box 48, Folder 1)
    bar code #: 3 1142 04227107 5
  - Security Committee: UCSL Subcommittee on Security, 1978-1979; 167848 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Security Committee: Senate Discussion of Security Committee Report, 1980; 167847 (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - Security Committee: Final Report, 1981; 167846 (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Security: Auxiliary Police Information, 1980; 167845 (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - Security, 1979-1981; 167844 (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - Security Committee: Minutes From Zone Visits, 1980; 167843 (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - NYU In The News, January-February, 1982-1983; 167842 (Box 48, Folder 8)
  - NYU In The News, November-December, 1982; 167841 (Box 48, Folder 9)
  - NYU In The News, Fall, 1982; 167840 (Box 48, Folder 10)
  - NYU In The News, March-April, 1982; 167839 (Box 48, Folder 11)
  - Policy and Planning, 1977-1982; 167838 (Box 48, Folder 12)
  - Planning/Long Range, 1979; 167837 (Box 48, Folder 13)
  - Martin Bernstein Hall, 1969-1973; 167836 (Box 48, Folder 14)
  - Professor Andre Beaumont (Deceased), 1974; 167835 (Box 48, Folder 15)
  - Dean's Meetings-Spring/Summer, 1981; 167834 (Box 48, Folder 16)
  - Dean's Meetings-Fall, 1980; 167833 (Box 48, Folder 17)
  - Dean's Meetings: Time and Effort Reporting (Faculty Policies), 1980; 167832 (Box 48, Folder 18)
  - Dean's Meetings-Spring/Summer, 1980; 167831 (Box 48, Folder 19)
  - Dean's Meeting-Agenda Item, Joseph C. Wilson Award Committee, 1979; 167830 (Box 48, Folder 20)
  - Dean's Meeting-Agenda: Space Management, 1978; 167829 (Box 48, Folder 21)
  - Dean's Meeting-Agenda Items-Faculty Staffing Policies and Procedure, 1978; 167828 (Box 48, Folder 22)
  - Dean's Meeting-Agenda Items-Telecommunications-Telephone, 1978; 167827 (Box 48, Folder 23)
  - Dean's Meeting-Animal Welfare Regulations, 1978; 167826 (Box 48, Folder 24)
  - Dean's Meeting-Implications of the Bakke Decision, 1978; 167825 (Box 48, Folder 25)
  - Dean's Meeting-Agenda Items: Capital Budgeting, 1978; 167824 (Box 48, Folder 26)
  - Dean's Meetings-Spring/Summer, 1979; 167823 (Box 48, Folder 27)
  - Dean's Meetings-Fall, 1979; 167822 (Box 48, Folder 28)
  - Dean's Meeting-Agenda Item, Time Modules, 1979; 167821 (Box 48, Folder 29)
  - Dean's Meeting-Agenda Item, NYU 150th Anniversary, 1979; 167820 (Box 48, Folder 30)
  - Dean's Meeting (Retirement Age), 1979; 167819 (Box 48, Folder 31)
  - Dean's Meetings, 1978; 167818 (Box 48, Folder 32)
  - Dean's Meeting-Agenda Items, Early Retirement and Individual Status Agreement, 1978; 167817 (Box 48, Folder 33)
  - Park, Joseph H. Honor Society, 1979-1980; 167816 (Box 48, Folder 34)
  - Medical Center-Financial Report, 1980; 167815 (Box 48, Folder 35)
  - Dean's Meetings, Fall, 1978; 167814 (Box 48, Folder 36)
  - Dean's Meetings, Spring, 1977; 167813 (Box 49, Folder 1)
    bar code #: 3 1142 04227108 3
  - Dean's Meetings, Fall, 1977; 167812 (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - Dean's Meetings, 1976; 167811 (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - Development Charitable Gift-Annuity, 1980-1981; 167810 (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - Development Donations, 1975-1978; 167809 (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - Development, 1980-1981; 167808 (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - Development Leadership Campaign, 1976-1979; 167807 (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - Senate, 1979-1980; 167806 (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - Senate, 1978-1979; 167805 (Box 49, Folder 9)
  - Senate, 1977-1978; 167804 (Box 49, Folder 10)
  - Senate, 1976-1977; 167803 (Box 49, Folder 11)
  - Senate, 1980-1981; 167802 (Box 49, Folder 12)
  - Senate-Rules of Procedure, undated; 167801 (Box 49, Folder 13)
  - GSAS-MA and MS Degrees, 1972-1975; 167800 (Box 50, Folder 1)
    bar code #: 3 1142 04227109 1
  - Degrees Conferred, October, 1972; 167799 (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - Degrees Conferred, February, 1973; 167798 (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - Degrees Conferred, June, 1973; 167797 (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - Degrees Conferred, October, 1973; 167796 (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - Degrees Conferred, February, 1974; 167795 (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - Degrees Conferred, June, 1974; 167794 (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - Degrees Conferred, October, 1974; 167793 (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - Degrees Conferred, February, 1975; 167792 (Box 50, Folder 9)
  - Degrees Conferred, June, 1975; 167791 (Box 50, Folder 10)
  - Degrees Conferred, October, 1975; 167790 (Box 50, Folder 11)
  - Degrees Conferred, February, 1976; 167789 (Box 50, Folder 12)
  - Degrees Conferred, June, 1976; 167788 (Box 50, Folder 13)
  - Degrees Conferred, October, 1976; 167787 (Box 50, Folder 14)
  - Degrees Conferred, February, 1977; 167786 (Box 50, Folder 15)
  - Degrees Conferred, June, 1977; 167785 (Box 50, Folder 16)
  - Degrees Conferred, 1978-1979; 167784 (Box 50, Folder 17)
  - Degrees, February, 1978; 167783 (Box 50, Folder 18)
  - Degrees Conferred, June, 1978; 167782 (Box 50, Folder 19)
  - Degrees Conferred, February, 1979; 167781 (Box 50, Folder 20)
  - Degrees Conferred, June, 1979; 167780 (Box 50, Folder 21)
  - GSAS-Degrees Granted, 1973-1974; 167779 (Box 50, Folder 22)
  - Degrees Granted, Academic Year, October-June, 1975-1976; 167778 (Box 50, Folder 23)
  - Degrees Granted, 1976-1977; 167777 (Box 50, Folder 24)
  - Degrees Granted, 1977-1978; 167776 (Box 50, Folder 25)
  - Degrees Granted, October, 1977; 167775 (Box 50, Folder 26)
  - Degrees Granted, October, 1977; 167774 (Box 50, Folder 27)
  - Degrees Granted, October, 1978; 167773 (Box 50, Folder 28)
  - Degrees Granted, October, 1979; 167772 (Box 50, Folder 29)
  - Certificates Awarded, June, 1979; 167771 (Box 50, Folder 30)
  - Point Count, Spring, 1965; 167770 (Box 50, Folder 31)
  - Point Count, Summer, 1965; 167769 (Box 50, Folder 32)
  - Point Count, Fall, 1964-1965; 167768 (Box 50, Folder 33)
  - Point Count, Spring, 1966; 167767 (Box 50, Folder 34)
  - Point Count, Summer, 1966; 167766 (Box 50, Folder 35)
  - Point Count, Fall, 1966; 167765 (Box 50, Folder 36)
  - Point Count, Spring, 1967; 167764 (Box 50, Folder 37)
  - Point Count, Summer, 1967; 167763 (Box 50, Folder 38)
  - Point Count, Fall, 1967; 167762 (Box 50, Folder 39)
  - Point Count, Spring, 1968; 167761 (Box 50, Folder 40)
  - Point Count, Summer, 1968; 167760 (Box 50, Folder 41)
  - Point Count, Fall, 1968; 167759 (Box 50, Folder 42)
  - Point Count, Spring, 1969; 167758 (Box 50, Folder 43)
  - Point Count, Summer, 1969; 167757 (Box 50, Folder 44)
  - Point Count, Fall, 1969; 167756 (Box 50, Folder 45)
  - Point Count, Spring, 1970; 167755 (Box 50, Folder 46)
  - Point Count, Summer, 1970; 167754 (Box 50, Folder 47)
  - Point Count, Fall, 1970; 167753 (Box 50, Folder 48)
  - Point Count, Spring, 1971; 167752 (Box 50, Folder 49)
  - Point Count, Summer, 1971; 167751 (Box 50, Folder 50)
  - Point Count, Fall, 1971; 167750 (Box 50, Folder 51)
  - Point Count, Spring, 1972; 167749 (Box 50, Folder 52)
  - Point Count, Summer, 1972; 167748 (Box 50, Folder 53)
  - Point Count, Fall, 1972; 167747 (Box 50, Folder 54)
  - Point Count, Spring, 1973; 167746 (Box 50, Folder 55)
  - Point Count, Summer, 1973; 167745 (Box 50, Folder 56)
  - Point Count, Fall, 1973; 167744 (Box 50, Folder 57)
  - Final Point Count, Spring, 1974; 167743 (Box 50, Folder 58)
  - Final Point Count, Summer, 1974; 167742 (Box 50, Folder 59)
  - Final Point Count, Fall, 1974; 167741 (Box 50, Folder 60)
  - Final Point Count, Spring, 1975; 167740 (Box 50, Folder 61)
  - Point Count, Summer, 1975; 167739 (Box 50, Folder 61)
  - Final Point Count, Fall, 1975; 167738 (Box 50, Folder 63)
  - Final Point Count, Spring, 1976; 167737 (Box 50, Folder 64)
  - Point Count Summer Sessions I & II, 1976; 167736 (Box 50, Folder 65)
  - Final Point Count Fall, 1976; 167735 (Box 50, Folder 66)
  - Final Point Count, Spring, 1977; 167734 (Box 50, Folder 67)
  - Point Count, Summer Session II, July, 1977; 167733 (Box 50, Folder 68)
  - Final Point Count, Fall, 1977; 167732 (Box 51, Folder 1)
    bar code #: 3 1142 04227110 9
  - Point Count, Spring, 1978; 167731 (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - Point Count, Summer Session I & II, 1978; 167730 (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - Point Count, Fall, 1978; 167729 (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - Point Count, Spring, 1979; 167728 (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - Point Count, Summer Session, 1979; 167727 (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - Point Count, Summer Registration, Summary, 1964-1978; 167726 (Box 51, Folder 7)
  - Point Count-Summer (Summary), 1963-1976; 167725 (Box 51, Folder 8)
  - Summer Session Point Count By Department, 1973-1978; 167724 (Box 51, Folder 9)
  - A, 1930-1955; 167723 (Box 51, Folder 10)
  - B, 1929-1955; 167722 (Box 51, Folder 11)
  - Barasch, Mrs. Frances (Woman Students), 1959; 167721 (Box 51, Folder 12)
  - Dean's Office (Baer), 1941; 167720 (Box 51, Folder 13)
  - Bookstore, 1947-1952; 167719 (Box 51, Folder 14)
  - C, 1930-1954; 167718 (Box 51, Folder 15)
  - Committee For Technology Center, 1958; 167717 (Box 51, Folder 16)
  - Curriculum Committee II, 1929-1947; 167716 (Box 51, Folder 17)
  - D-Prior to 1954, 1934-1954; 167715 (Box 51, Folder 18)
  - Dean Baer, 1949-1957; 167714 (Box 51, Folder 19)
  - Dean's Cabinet, 1936-1959; 167713 (Box 51, Folder 20)
  - E-Prior to 1954, 1946-1953; 167712 (Box 51, Folder 21)
  - F-Prior to 1954, 1932-1954; 167711 (Box 51, Folder 22)
  - G-Prior to 1954, 1948-1953; 167710 (Box 51, Folder 23)
  - H-Prior to 1954, 1935-1954; 167709 (Box 51, Folder 24)
  - I-Prior to 1954, 1943-1953; 167708 (Box 51, Folder 25)
  - J-Prior to 1954, 1945-1954; 167707 (Box 51, Folder 26)
  - K-Prior to 1954, 1932-1954; 167706 (Box 51, Folder 27)
  - Dean John W. Knedler, Jr., 1962-1963; 167705 (Box 51, Folder 28)
  - Dean John W. Knedler, Jr., 1946-1960; 167704 (Box 51, Folder 29)
  - Future Proposals Sent to Dean Knedler, 1960-1961; 167703 (Box 51, Folder 30)
  - L-Prior to 1954, 1936-1954; 167702 (Box 51, Folder 31)
  - Library-Society for the Libraries, 1938-1961; 167701 (Box 51, Folder 32)
  - M-Prior to 1954, 1937-1953; 167700 (Box 51, Folder 33)
  - Mc-Prior to 1954, 1947-1951; 167699 (Box 51, Folder 34)
  - Modern Language Exam, 1929-1941; 167698 (Box 51, Folder 35)
  - N-Prior to 1954, 1931-1954; 167697 (Box 51, Folder 36)
  - NYU's Program for Leadership and Service in the Sixties, undated; 167696 (Box 51, Folder 37)
  - President Newsom, 1957-1961; 167695 (Box 51, Folder 38)
  - O-Prior to 1954, 1947-1952; 167694 (Box 51, Folder 39)
  - P-Prior to 1954, 1931-1953; 167693 (Box 51, Folder 40)
  - PT and S, 1939/1940; 167692 (Box 52, Folder 1)
    bar code #: 3 1142 04227111 7
  - Q-Prior to 1954, 1940-1949; 167691 (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - R-Prior to 1954, 1931-1954; 167690 (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - Rapid Advancement Program, 1959; 167689 (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - Recommendations, 1947-1961; 167688 (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - Registration Report, 1947-1957; 167687 (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - S-Prior to 1954, 1939-1954; 167686 (Box 52, Folder 7)
  - S-Prior to 1954, 1931-1954; 167685 (Box 52, Folder 8)
  - Self Study Committee, 1955; 167684 (Box 52, Folder 9)
  - Dean's Still, 1958-1960; 167683 (Box 52, Folder 10)
  - Survey Committee, 1937; 167682 (Box 52, Folder 11)
  - T-Prior to 1954, 1931-1954; 167681 (Box 52, Folder 12)
  - Television and Radio, 1957-1960; 167680 (Box 52, Folder 13)
  - Tenure-Committee On, 1938-1939; 167679 (Box 52, Folder 14)
  - Testing and Advisement-New Forms, 1948-1962; 167678 (Box 52, Folder 15)
  - Tutorial (Dean Cullen), Summer, 1958-1959; 167677 (Box 52, Folder 16)
  - U-1954 and Prior, 1934-1952; 167676 (Box 52, Folder 17)
  - Undergraduate Scholarship Committee, 1947; 167675 (Box 52, Folder 18)
  - V-1954 and Prior, 1932-1952; 167674 (Box 52, Folder 19)
  - VA Data, 1946; 167673 (Box 52, Folder 20)
  - VA Data, 1944; 167672 (Box 52, Folder 21)
  - W-1954 and Prior, 1929-1959; 167671 (Box 52, Folder 22)
  - Y-1954 and Prior, 1929-1953; 167670 (Box 52, Folder 23)
  - Z-1954 and Prior, 1935-1947; 167669 (Box 52, Folder 24)
  - AAVP, 1972; 167668 (Box 52, Folder 25)
  - Annual Report of the Dean, 1970-1971; 167667 (Box 52, Folder 26)
  - Comm, Law School Recommendations, 1970; 167666 (Box 52, Folder 27)
  - Codes for Educational Institutions, 1972; 167665 (Box 52, Folder 28)
  - Doctorate Records File, 1973; 167664 (Box 52, Folder 29)
  - EEPC, 1970-1971; 167663 (Box 52, Folder 30)
  - FAC Meetings, 1970-1971; 167662 (Box 52, Folder 31)
  - GNY Campaign, 1970-1971; 167661 (Box 52, Folder 32)
  - General Correspondence, 1970-1971; 167660 (Box 52, Folder 33)
  - Graduate School Alumni, 1971; 167659 (Box 52, Folder 34)
  - History Department, 1970-1973; 167658 (Box 52, Folder 35)
  - MAAS Essay, 1972; 167657 (Box 52, Folder 36)
  - Miscellaneous, 1971; 167656 (Box 52, Folder 37)
  - Recommendations, 1970-1973; 167655 (Box 52, Folder 38)
  - Student Faculty Advisory Committee, 1971; 167654 (Box 52, Folder 39)
  - University Admissions, 1971-1972; 167653 (Box 52, Folder 40)
  - University College, 1970-1973; 167652 (Box 52, Folder 41)
  - Alumni Newspapers, 1972-1977; 167651 (Box 53, Folder data_value_missing_50aef083c9ff8afd23c527c17823f377)
    bar code #: 3 1142 04227471 5
  - Cutler, Max, 1967-1968; 167650 (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - Dansforth Foundation, 1964-1975; 167649 (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - Dansforth Literature & Annual Reports, 1970-1974; 167648 (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - Da Ponte, Marcia, 1975; 167647 (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - Data Processing Unit, 1968-1969; 167646 (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - Chee Davis, 1970; 167645 (Box 53, Folder 7)
  - Dean's Advisory Group, 1974-1975; 167644 (Box 53, Folder 8)
  - Outgoing correspondence, 2000; 167643 (Box 53, Folder 9)
  - Dean's Council Minutes, 1969-1970; 167642 (Box 53, Folder 10)
  - Dean's Council French Study in France, 1970-; 167641 (Box 53, Folder 11)
  - Dean's Council Visiting Committee, 1972-; 167640 (Box 53, Folder 12)
  - Dean's Council Dean's Lecture Series, 1968-; 167639 (Box 53, Folder 13)
  - Deans Council Minutes/Agenda's, 1974-1976; 167638 (Box 53, Folder 14)
  - Dean's Council Minutes, Agenda, Notes, 1975-, undated; 167637 (Box 53, Folder 15)
  - Dean of Faculty of A & S, 1973-; 167635 (Box 53, Folder 17)
  - Dean's List, 1967-1970; 167634 (Box 53, Folder 18)
  - Deanship, WSC, 1968-; 167633 (Box 53, Folder 19)
  - Dean, Vera, 1961-1967; 167632 (Box 53, Folder 20)
  - Debate Team, 1963-1966; 167631 (Box 53, Folder 21)
  - Degree Candidates; Graduates, 1971-1972; 167630 (Box 53, Folder 22)
  - Degree Program, Three -year, 1971-1972; 167629 (Box 53, Folder 23)
  - Ad Hoc Committee on Discipline, 1968-1976; 167628 (Box 53, Folder 24)
  - Discipline Policy, 1947-1970; 167627 (Box 53, Folder 25)
  - Discipline Policy, 1968-1969; 167626 (Box 53, Folder 26)
  - Senate: Discipline Procedures, 1968-1969; 167625 (Box 53, Folder 27)
  - Disciplinary Panel Hearings, 1974; 167624 (Box 53, Folder 28)
  - Student Disciplinary Proceedings at NYU (adopted by Senate 11/12/1970), 167623 (Box 53, Folder 29)
  - Disruption, 1968-1970; 167622 (Box 53, Folder 30)
  - Student Disorders: Analysis, 1969; 167621 (Box 53, Folder 31)
  - Distinctive Roll, 1963; 167620 (Box 53, Folder 32)
  - Doctoral Council, New York State, 1974-1975; 167619 (Box 53, Folder 33)
  - Distiguished Professorships, 1964-1968; 167618 (Box 53, Folder 34)
  - Dow Chemical Corporation, 1968; 167617 (Box 53, Folder 35)
  - Draft, 1973; 167616 (Box 53, Folder 36)
  - Draft Classification, 1967-1968; 167615 (Box 53, Folder 37)
  - Dress, 1964; 167614 (Box 53, Folder 38)
  - Dramatic Literature, 1967-1975; 167613 (Box 53, Folder 39)
  - Dreyfuss, Camille & Henry Foundation Proposal, 1975; 167612 (Box 53, Folder 40)
  - Drugs, 1971; 167611 (Box 53, Folder 41)
  - Dual Major, 1967; 167610 (Box 53, Folder 42)
  - Duplication of Courses, 1969-1974; 167609 (Box 53, Folder 43)
  - E miscellaneous, 1964-1969; 167608 (Box 53, Folder 44)
  - Education Policy Committee Reports, 1963-1967; 167607 (Box 53, Folder 45)
  - Education Professions Development Act, 1965-1970; 167606 (Box 53, Folder 46)
  - Early Decisions at NYU Medical, 1973; 167605 (Box 53, Folder 47)
  - Economics, 1966-1975; 167604 (Box 53, Folder 48)
  - Enviromental Science and Engineering Group, 1969; 167603 (Box 53, Folder 49)
  - Econmics Brochure, 1975; 167602 (Box 53, Folder 50)
  - Evening College of Arts & Science, 1966-1968; 167601 (Box 53, Folder 51)
  - Evening Division, 1962-1965; 167600 (Box 53, Folder 52)
  - Cutler, Max, 1967-1968; 167599 (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - Dansforth Foundation, 1964-1975; 167598 (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - Dansforth Literature & Annual Reports, 1970-1974; 167597 (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - Da Ponte, Marcia, 1975; 167596 (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - Data Processing Unit, 1968-1969; 167595 (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - Chee Davis, 1970; 167594 (Box 53, Folder 7)
  - Dean's Advisory Group, 1974-1975; 167593 (Box 53, Folder 8)
  - Outgoing correspondence, 2000; 167592 (Box 53, Folder 9)
  - Dean's Council Minutes, 1969-1970; 167591 (Box 53, Folder 10)
  - Dean's Council French Study in France, 1970-; 167590 (Box 53, Folder 11)
  - Dean's Council Visiting Committee, 1972-; 167589 (Box 53, Folder 12)